wealthwire.com 2011-06-08

# Wealth Wire - Subscription Management

Subscription Info and Tools

In order to ensure that you receive each issue of Wealth Wire, please add **ww-eletter@angelnexus.com** to your address book or to your safe-list in your spam filter settings. 

Not currently subscribed? [Click here](http://wealthwire.com/subscribe)! 

If you have suggestions for improvement, please [let us know](http://wealthwire.com/contact). 

* * *

**Menu**

  * View Privacy Policy
  * Update Your Email Address
  * End Membership
  * Addresses and Phone Numbers

* * *

**Privacy Policy**   
We have created this privacy policy to guarantee our firm commitment to your privacy and the protection of your information. 

  * **Why did I receive an email from you?**   
If you received a mailing from us, either a) your email address is listed with us as belonging to someone who has expressly requested receipt of information in the future ("opt-in"), or b) you have registered with, purchased from or otherwise have an existing relationship with us. 
  * **What's your policy regarding sharing and usage?**   
We will never share, sell, or rent individual personal information to/with anyone without your advance permission unless ordered by a court of law. Information submitted to us is only available a) to employees managing this information for the purpose of contacting you regarding your subscription or a request made by you for information, or b) to contracted service providers for the purpose of providing services relating to our communications with you. 
  * **Third-Party Web Beacons**   
We use third-party web beacons from Yahoo! to help analyze where visitors go and what they do while visiting our website. Yahoo! may also use anonymous information about your visits to this and other websites in order to improve its products and services and provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by Yahoo!, [click here](https://reports.web.analytics.yahoo.com/optout,OptOut.vm). 
  * **How do you protect my privacy?**   
We employ security measures above and beyond industry standards to protect against the loss, misuse or alteration of your personal data. 
  * **How can I stop receiving email from you?**   
Each email sent contains a link to our easy, automated system for subscription management. If you wish to unsubscribe, simply follow this link anytime. To unsubscribe now, enter your email address below. Your email address will then be immediately removed from our mailings. 
  * **How can I report abuse?**   
Simply fill out the form located here. 

* * *

**Update Your Email Address**   
Fill out the form below to update the email address to which Wealth Wire is sent. 

* * *

**End Membership**   
Enter your email address below to end your membership with Wealth Wire. 

* * *

**Addresses and Phone Numbers**

  * **_Mailing_**   
P.O. Box 84905   
Phoenix, AZ 85071 

  * **_Physical_**   
10000 N 31st Ave, Ste 102   
Phoenix, AZ 85051 

  * Telephone: +1 877.528.2645   
Facsimile: +1 602.943.2363
